and mirror the cast of shadow every shadow
pretend quiet symbol by the stare with constellations in her hair
she asked me what i knew for sure i answered nothing
face i should space
in so wherever it is and wherever you may or may not be
in this bass world i'm your host psychy and i just wanted to talk about a few things today
but I'm not gonna talk until somebody talks in my chat.
I'll just sit here silently waiting.
Hey J-Dog, how are you?
Yeah, so I'll put up my, okay, talk,
so I will put up my link, and we can have a discussion
if you'd like to, or anybody else.
Of course, we have rules applying.
No docs thing, no actionable slander.
Just the truth, which is,
Interesting about hi thing that is. How are you? Good to see you. Thanks for being here. You can come up. I'd appreciate it, too
That's been bad, you know
There may not be family members or or that I'm saying that I need to be institutionalized
Christine's in there Christine to donate her. Oh, sorry. Don't know to donate. She deleted her comments
You know where she said she was going to be you misusing her her medical access in order to
try to have me
institutionalized or
Something along those lines. She's in there right now. Also. It's kind of interesting, you know
I'm responding just to what's being said right now
But you know, I have all I've been doing is responding and this person is saying oh well don't talk about me
But I'm responding to what's being said and wow. I'm telling the truth. This person is telling all lies
You know, it's unfortunate that I mean
I mean, there's a point to freedom of speech.
Of course, you know, it's a great,
it's a great, wonderful thing we have in this country,
but there's also misuse of freedom of speech.
There are such things as sharing private information,
whether there's, you know, profiles
on the social media profiles that are 10 years old
or whatever, like around, hey, we have J.Dog coming in.
Did I say key? What's up, dude? How are you doing? I'm okay. How are you doing? Oh, I'm chilling, bro
What's wrong dude? You sound like something's up like something's wrong with you. What happened, man?
No, you don't see what's being broadcast right now
No, oh is somebody putting you on blast like they trying to blast put your your private stuff out there
I'll just put backstage. Just go check out this channel if you can come back
Check out that channel real quick. Okay. Okay. I'll be right back. Let me see. Thank you
Yeah, Katrina. I think you're you're absolutely right about that and I mean it's gotten to such a point where I mean, I mean
it's
it's you know, I feel it's gonna need to a dangerous place and
You know almost that kind of
I almost wish I was kind of a thug like some of these people, you know,
because they handle things a little bit differently, but, you know, I have the option of,
okay, she's not, well, it's still up there.
It's still up there.
Bay, it's still up there.
Bay clips.
But anyway, yeah, well, that's the second of today, and she will be going again, I guess,
again tonight.
You know, I always, I talked to her.
I did agree with somebody.
I was like, yeah, I'm just going to, you know.
Oh, okay
Dude she put up that I'm not even gonna say what it is, but I saw
Yeah, I don't need to say what's up there
Already already
Filed over you so yeah
I'm sorry about that. I'm sorry if that's happening right now. I'd like she's going so overboard with this shit
She's in there with Christine saying that I have a tapeworm as the newest here
That's why I'm so bad. I don't have a tapeworm
Tapeworm yeah, don't you have to go like to a foreign country to get that like Costa Rica or something like that and like eat
Something that drink the water or something you see and use for medical expertise to
to, to, to surmise that, uh, it's possibly from the picture, and cat fleas or something like that, I've cut, I've cut a tapeworm from cat fleas or something like that.
Then everybody would have a tapeworm, if that's the case, because everybody has cats.
Right. I mean, it's like, I'm not saying people are smart, uh, I'm just saying, that's what they're saying. I mean, it's like...
Dude, you know why? Dude, you don't let her get you down, dude. Fuck that bitch. Fuck Christine, fuck Alex.
They're just keming up bro before she was trying to say, um, you need to go, uh, what did she say bungee jump off a bridge or some
Jump off the bridge, okay, okay
In my post, my community, while I did, I asked Chachi P. at the person who were comments
of Christine's comments, and I said, it's this ethical for a nurse to be saying this publicly,
jump off a bridge, that hurting me would have no karmic consequences, and that killing me
would, no jury would convict her because I'm such a bad person. And so that's the first
and nursing, uh, board of nurses or whatever should be, um,
immediately investigating this woman. And so if you could help me out,
get a lay job with the last name for this woman, Christine,
or any information, because, um, I need to be contacted with a nursing
board immediately about you. You, you, when you need her
docs, I could, I can probably get ahold of that. Thank you.
I could probably, yeah, I could probably. We'll talk back. We'll talk to you after.
Oh, okay, okay. Yeah, I'm going to put my email address for you.
Thank you so much appreciate that
She's dogs by the way, she's doxing eldo today
For skiing doxeldo today. No, I'm the other person the other person. Oh, okay. Okay. The jezebel. Okay. Yeah, okay
Okay, which is like I would just say she's a jezebel spirit because it is pretty much in control right now. I actually did
have a
Have a psychic reading
And without any prompting
Jezebel came right up right up
and also along with Legion.
region and so many demons many demons controlling this woman not just one
It's like we can get the supernatural it's hard to prove supernatural charges
You know I'm more into the supernatural
But I mean if she can say that I'm a werewolf and then a demon and she can name
specific kings of hell that I'm supposedly aligned with and working with and then putting sigils of certain angels
If she thinks we'll cancel out the demon. It's a little bit like
Dungeons and Dragons at this point. Yeah
Magic and gathering. I mean, it's like, I don't know because I thought Sandman was the only one that played kids games like that
Card kid kid card games. Yeah. Oh, you know what? Oh, and if you don't want to annoy Sandman
Listen, I was in his chat yesterday
Being annoying as fuck, right?
You get it on purpose
But you know what I got him
What happened I said he plays kids games. Oh
So that struck a nerve right there. Oh
So that hit close to the heart
yeah so you know see I mean I thought you were new about trolling like you know it's like you
don't kind of come away uh what uh what bothers you but I guess that struck a nerve with uh Mr
public figure Samuel Torres okay so we have um we have another guest here this one is slugger
Sam and so I'm on one second I need to make it start first right first one's good
Crystal. Yeah, okay. It's you. Okay
Okay, that's a real crystal
Who sends concrete what I know about who sends concrete? It was it was this person named Tony the conductor
I don't know if it was him 100% of the time said he it to me
I know Q does the same thing Q does it too, but yeah Tony the conductor
Basically took credit for all of it. He was actually indicted on May 6th or criminal criminal harassment
And sending conceals houses and so he stopped
I think the one who did to me was definitely gamble
Okay, gamble. Yeah. I mean, if he's working with Q maybe, I mean, Q, I mean, these are like
Q wouldn't, Q wouldn't just fuck with me just to put, but you know, like, uh,
So how much did they send? I mean, I'm not, if you don't mind, if you don't want to tell me, it's fine.
I don't want to talk about it. Okay, you don't want to talk about it. Okay. But yeah, I just want to tell you,
um, first of all, I did get like about 40, 40 bags of concrete on around Christmas time,
put it on my front step. They had a door dash. People bring it. They, they told the door dash
people that I'm insane and that was they don't put it down. And so they would just say,
off you um rg i guess black rg uh i like rg though like he's cool okay well look we
don't have to talk about he's not a lot on the show anymore but yeah um j dog okay so
i just posted the recording of mod y right and they're saying he wanted a f of 14 year old
what the fuck yeah
Was he drunk or he was just like like he just said it like drunk or not the fact that he said it and then no
No, yeah, there's no excuse for it. I he said in my chat. He was gonna continue saying that
But you can go listen to it. Oh, yeah, I'll definitely check it out. So look at so if you'd like bring our bq
He's just like him
He's the one that break bq into my life
Yeah, other girls life and those other girls like the other girl you're talking about Lindsey
And the Kayla like the recording wasn't even that bad. Honestly. I don't like him
I think gamble was 100% a predator. He has great on people's kids before he has done shit
I want to say he's like pdf, but he's definitely a predator. Oh, yeah
Yeah, and yesterday I know Jay dog you you like exited the proof of him saying he would make another POF account of me
so the mining gables beef go way back years ago years ago and the amount of
all that he has that he will do it's gonna be all documented but I just
say it just say that and report it I saw you got a bitch you need to like get
like a you know how did you feel that he went on say a man's live like and they
were like you know doing this whole like weird thing oh yeah I feel like that
Psyche was just saying I think Sandman they hit a nerve when it come to the child thing and that's why
Yes, there's like a connection there like maybe they put each other up to it
Like because why did he go from yours to Sandman's like he's like almost the same kind of I'm kind of confused of it
Like what exactly is going on all I heard was somebody underage
Okay, so I just want to address that yesterday that girl showed me her ID. She is not she's not underage
She is an adult. I thought I was a guy. Well, what's like you're getting them all?
No, oh, you know, they're you know, they're accusing me a brand in Q is over my discord saying that I had like I'm
I'm a pet of files
Well, let me let me turn this thing off for this. What's what's going on with this thing?
Here's the thing if it wasn't for fucking gamble, we wouldn't be dealing with freaking branding here
Well, how did he come over here from the beginning with, because from what I understand, he brought him up into the fucking chat like he did to Lindsay's in December when I was in the round, just like he did to me.
And honestly, I blame Gamble for Braining Q. You want to know why? Two and a half years ago, maybe three years ago, right?
On a call, which I had those recordings, by the way, and then they're saying telling him to say that he's gonna do all these, like, terroristic threats and shit, right?
Two-nine-one-one dispatch. So then when they swatted Brandon, gamble. You just fucking protected Gamble.
Damn.
I gave him power. So fuck you, Gamble. Fuck you.
Because why would you get oofy set up if oofy's not the predator and the other predator like what what are you doing?
You're fucking insane, dude
They're just predators. That's all they are
After pedophiles and shit you fucking expose him. Oh and docks him and his shows also and all that shit, right?
You are such a
And you're a scared little bitch
Are you guys?
Let me let me ask you this. Are you guys catching predators?
What's happening? I'm going after Gamble for causing a fucking shit storm in all these communities because he thinks he's so
He brought in the eggs. He brought in the eggs that is known as bq. Yep. He brought in
Clearly does not give a fuck. Oh, yeah. No, that's another one. That's another one right there. Mogwai. Yep
And that's not exposing that shit because I'm like, dude, none of us wanted to be wrapped up in this shit at all.
Yeah.
Right.
You got it.
I'll do it.
This shit got hella dirty.
I mean, no matter our differences, Crystal, you know, I would never like, you know, I'm not the type of person to go to do this kind of, this stuff.
I mean, it's like, you know, and so it's like.
Well, here's the thing.
Okay.
When you go to an interrogation room, are you going to like go at them?
Are you going to try to collect intel?
Who are you talking about, myself?
No, just in general.
Oh, in general.
Well, it's like kind of you maybe you want to.
Right, you act freely towards them, right?
That's exactly what I want for Brandon Q.
Because I knew Gamble was deep down into this shit
when I remember some of the shit.
And I was like, you know what, fuck Gamble.
Because honestly, me and Lindsay and my friends,
we wouldn't have had to deal with Brandon Q.
I didn't know Brandon Q was going to.
And maybe tonight expose Brandon Q on Instagram.
Another platform that gamble never exposed them on
Yeah, I know that name. Why do I know that name Brandon Q? Yeah, that's a little pop
He's a sick motherfucker stay away from him wherever he's at. Just go the other way. Yeah, stay away
That name rings a bell for sure. Yeah
brain and Q can all talk together and not have any repercussions.
Make it make sense.
I know.
Because they're all talking about it, you know, I had Brandon on my show
and I and Crystal, but it was for the same reason I was basically trying
to collect intelligence about it.
Like I was trying to let him expose himself.
They don't know anything.
He only knows whatever Gamble says, but he now, but he knows what I'm saying
is fucking true, so he better fucking watch it.
Right.
Right, and Crystal lands on saying she's like trying to be a hero or you know, like they are they're all they're all trying to be like these
No, they're trying to manipulate that audio. Yeah, totally. Okay. I have my own community outside of the panel first
that they didn't know this guy clearly they're gonna wait until they get their own proof and not go
based off of what gamble says because gamble is a very manipulative and he has harassed these women
before and other people right so they're gonna wait until they get their own proof yeah gamble is
one of those gay guys that is like real bitchy and like well here's the thing why didn't he use my panel
to weaponize Brandon Q.
Why couldn't he use his own fucking panel?
Right, because it's like, it's just like
Dita using my panel to do all kinds of herbed
or do-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Good, good, good, right there.
I know, guess what?
I guess Kate wants to eat blood fishes.
Oh, well eat all the blood fishes you want this week
because it's apparently Red Lobster over here.
You, they can't be talking about nobody.
Kate looks like a blowfish.
I don't know why she's putting your face on.
I mean, Kate looks like literally,
I mean, I have-
Just tell us some Lindsay, clear as day.
Yeah, I do have this picture of of you know of Kate. This is actually she is on our show
You know the thing is I tried really I tried really hard to just forgive gamble and forgive and forget
But you can't you cannot forgive him like there is no forgiving subconsciously
There you go. There's there's beautiful Kate. There's Kate the turtle. Yeah, but they're like I don't
I don't agree with like that's a public figure. It's a public picture. She's well. She's got on camera before crystal
Okay, it's just her picture. That's her on camera
I don't want any fuck shit happening to me because you did that. Hey
Well, you know talk about going low she said she was saying the other night eating my cats
Crystal, you know, so but the thing is is all this shit
Because here's the thing, it wasn't my gamble.
He's always going to be online is because he got charged with two terrorists to
That's never gonna give you a career
They're always gonna do a background check and see that even if it goes even if you get it explained
Any background check so you ruined your fucking career over trolling people you dumb ass gamble
No one should be taking notes for me
Hey, and you know and now be that Sam and I've broken up, you know the honeymoon's over there
Their e relationship is over
Okay, so I don't understand. Oh, J-Dog, when I'm in peace with Vita, correct?
Denicate, and all of them give me a hard time about it.
Yes, 100%.
They attack you for it. They attack you for it. That's what they were trying to do.
piece and it's like, Oh,
in the community and it's
kind of a bigger audience
But so it's like, you kno
get away with that kind o
standards and you know be
exact thing. Well, here's
Gamble legit did revenge porn on me last night because he was triggered this when Gamble gets triggered. That's what he does
You couldn't win the argument with me you porn bombs me
What do you porn bomb you with?
Oh and bombs me because Lindsay was talking shit about her because you were talking shit about her man
That's what they do. Yeah
I mean it gets so crazy so I'm going to end it now there's so many moving parts and pieces
oh what crazy is you know I had to tell brandy q to leave clumsy alone like stop he was showing the
documents you know to my community I was like dude stop it like what the heck what a creep
What a fucking cool
I tried to go on clumsies the other night and he he had me for a second
He looked like he he looked like a like a a scorned next girlfriend actually the face that he was making
Made fun of a child who had cancer. Oh, oh my god. Oh, no, that's low
Because game little guy his ego all big up and everything and he was like trying to play like he was John and Depp in a fucking
And also Gamble, why does your girlfriend, your fiance, look like she's barely 19?
I know, and Trippin' Step 2, that guy's a terrible, terrible, terrible guy.
Like, you're 30 years old, Gamble, and you look like you're with a 19-year-old, barely legal.
maybe the 19 right I mean it's like you know and it's like okay I'm more
prone to say you know but gamble loves people that he can fucking control right
and that's yeah and that's a form of grooming you dickhead yeah that's what
and also people like you know that go after people that kind of like
have like kind of like a gamble is around what do you fucking mean the people
saying gamble is not around he has 1000% around yeah well that is our way and I
blame him for brandon q's shit does he fucking if he never mentioned me to
brandon q bring I wouldn't be on brandon q's radar yeah
And I don't know and Brandon Q is the kind of person like I mean he like he basically comes to create chaos and then it's like
You know, I guess that was one good point about it. Is that that uh, no, I didn't West Coast
I can't collect intel to protect my community
I explained it over and over and over again the people that have listened said it wasn't even that bad of an audio
Like what are people stripping out? They just want to attack me to attack me
Because gamble can't fucking take any accountability
We have a we have a free site has come into the chat today. Let's welcome free side to the show
What up psyche?
What's popping from sign? What's up?
Crystal where's my fucking money hoe?
Yeah, well, I'm gonna need my 350 Ricky tan
I've been hearing that rumor around that they were trying to say that they're trying to say that you and Brandon Q
Like had like private DMs and shit like that
Instead of like a discord VC I had it my own cuz so
my wife
Me being a dumbass added
Why would you do that?
Because I didn't know this side of him. I don't I didn't know this evil side of him. Yeah, he's crazy
So he added brain and Q and I removed brain and Q so fucking fast, right?
And then next thing I know like and I'm arguing with Mogwai and the Mogwai goes
I wanted to know why he's following me like to gamble to send him and then other girls were like in my chat
We're like, yeah, he started following me too. What the fuck? So then we added them back to the chat, right?
And I was just basically trying to explain to him, like, the girls that I'm around with, we have nothing to do with Gamble, right?
We don't do any of this shit, we leave us alone, right?
So, and it was more like, yes, I should talk Gamble, because I was blaming Gamble for everything, because I do blame Gamble for everything, and I blame Mogwai for everything.
Why wouldn't he fucking do that? And then Alex from New York didn't even know and was all like
But then it only got real to them when he brought up my friend's toddler, you know
So when I nuked the chat he started calling my phone, right I declined every single one of them and
Messaged me threatening me
Oh, that I was around him?
Like, can I not fucking get intel from him?
But fuck Gamble.
I'm always gonna say fuck Gamble.
He used my platform to use me as a weapon against Brandon,
and that was his beef,
and he can fuck all the way off to fucking Pluto.
Internet.
There's no chatters. There's plenty of chatters. I hear there's a good chat right now. There's a good a number in the chat
I don't know what they're talking about. They go ahead Chris. I'm sorry to interrupt, but
Anyways, so people want to go ahead and be like, are you kicking it up?
Well, there's other people's voices in that call and
Honestly, I still feel that way. I'm not afraid to say it to people's faces
No, I was like the reason why I didn't tell anyone
About it out of that group chat was because it was no one's business. He was threatening my friends, too
And I was trying to protect their privacy.
Yeah, so we have a need of love.
Excuse me for being a good fucking friend and sticking my neck out there.
Because that's how I've always been.
I have a huge heart, but fuck you Gamble.
You have tormented these women.
It was like, almost like you planned all this shit.
Yeah
I don't know how I got involved in this situation either like it, you know
I'm not really like a brand and then Karen has a nerve to pose. Oh, Crystal is around a petto not like that
Not like you were Karen
Well, you know having me on a live and I know you paid Brandon Q
Yeah, as much as he says he did it. I know you did and he threatened to unalive all my friends on a daily
I know
I mean, it's like wow it's like there's so much going on with I mean
But my friends care about me too, you know, like my supporters care about me. They don't want me to just go down
A lot of them are scared of gamble because of what gamble is done to them and what is he done
What is the worst thing he has done what they're so scared about what dog scenes and what dogs?
Bringing up their names and then dragging them through
Bullshit again, and that's why they all went to Wilbur to get away
Gamble literally screams like a fucking lunatic. No VCs with Wilbur because he couldn't handle that. They didn't like him anymore
Gamble hates
Rejection you reject him and he doesn't know what the fuck to do with himself
I have no issues with Anita and he's that gamble
Is that trip right there? Or what is it? Trip is it right there.
I don't give a fuck who's gonna be mad at who I think this whole community got fucked with my brandy Q
And it wasn't none of our fault gamble. That was your shit your beam you involved everyone else with that shit
Yeah, he said honestly Sam and is so stupid. He's bringing it up
He said he got a kid to call in a swat and directed them. It's all on video. Wow
Wilbur never did that. He said that that you got a kid to call in a swat and he directed them how to do it on video
And well, Samman has, you know, Samman has death syndrome, guys, I mean, wait, Samman or Gamble?
No, they were saying Gamble. Get that. Yeah, I'm surprised.
Samman has death syndrome. Well, why did Gamble talk to a 12-year-old on his public platform about adult stuff,
like, oh, drugs and other stuff, and alcohol and all that stuff, huh? I just want my fear to be crippled.
I didn't do nothing, freeside.
They're trying to say you hate bonding wouldn't gamble. That's what they're saying. You hate bonding
I don't like gamble and I don't like brain and cue. Where am I hate bonding?
You said I said we said that shoot that you were on the call right here trip is saying you were on the call
Okay, I heard people were in that call you act like it was a it was an ID group call you dumbass
Was this the day sex said man was on the call they're saying said man and then
Okay, okay
No, that's what that's what tripp is saying. I'm not saying it. I don't know anything about this
I'm just you know what you're a disappointment. Eldo
Eldo, you know, you got Docs today, you know
They put a
They fake but it's not even a big deal. Everybody got gix-docs. It's like not a big thing. It's just you know
Anyways, this goes all the way back to like 2020 maybe even before that when I wasn't around
But I know the part that was around for and you know what why is Michael De Fay not even in jail still?
Gamble answer that question gamble
You wanted to blame him and then you wanted to blame Wilbur and then you wanted to blame other people and here's the thing
The reason why I know Wilbur is innocent is because Bruno Wilbur yellow. We're all friends
And none of them did fuck kiddo shit and by you
Gamble love to protect groomer Dee Dee remember her and I have a photo where she groomed Bruno's younger brother
You dumb fuck gamble
What's up with you protecting fucking weirdos gamble you protect mongwai you you're dead
You definitely did some dumb shit with oofy that it backfired
If you look at Kate's in the chat and then Sid wants a link SIG is asking for a link in Kate
I'm not talking to Kate
Look what Kate says Kate says doesn't matter how many people were on the call. We heard you
You want to be leather face? It's all good. Just eat me away all week because you want to eat my dinner, right?
You want me for dinner, right? I bet I taste it
Well, anyone else want to eat me all week? Just you know, it's red lobster week, I guess
All the blood fish you can eat
Blowfish blowfish Wednesdays, right? And that's the thing you have to say. Oh, she's mentally bad
Okay, you know what aren't you don't you have mental disorder?
Okay. Hey, we have 60 in the chat. You're mentally ill too, Kate.
Hit the print, hit bow, create. I just seen her on set. I thought Kate and Sandman
hated each other. Now she was up there with Kate. Kate was up there with Sandman and Bita,
her two most enemies that she hated the most. Oh yeah, oh yeah, to hate one again for me.
Yeah, that's how I was sitting and I was like, wow. Right?
Yeah, I will say this. Thank you clumsy for not attacking me actually and you J-Dog for this shit that happened
Yeah
Hello
They're gonna play billy bull. Oh
Are you there? Oh, I'll go
Is this that's elder elder are you there?
They don't why the fuck you dox me mega. I didn't dox you
Eldo, why are you making up like about me?
Cuz you fucking lot is that same man wasn't in the fucking a call when it was
But that one point he was in the chat with my white-eyed brain to give you dumb fuck. So are you
That don't matter why you want on a phone call instagram phone call
You weird
Fuck you or you're fucked
You wear for that
Nobody gives a flying fuck about you. You fucking know he cares about you who even are you?
Who the fuck are you shut up?
I'm not, you dumb fuck, I haven't bought it before, why are you trying to stay like I was talking to him when I'm the one who protects him, why are you protecting him, why are you shooting fucking ears, why did you use my platform
Come on, this is like, hey, Gamble, I challenge you, Gamble, Gamble, no, no, Gamble, why don't you go use your YouTube channel, go use your YouTube channel, open up the screen, I'm talking about on your channel, talk about on your fucking channel, you don't even have a pain in the shit.
I just
What's the 10-year-old's name?
Some girl?
What did you say?
Crystal!
Maybe you were going to report psyche?
You said you were going to take down anal?
YouTube, Crystalline.
The fucking loser!
I'll lose that for a second.
Sorry, guys.
Four videos.
You're posting me.
Post me.
No, I don't.
I don't even know what your TikTok is.
So, I'm just going to be talking about yours.
Crystal.
I just submitted four complaints against you check your email well if you don't take them down your channel is going bye-bye to
Good good, I'm gonna tell fish age don't worry
Panel streamer and you're posting me I can report you posting me dumb bitch. It's not your lives. I'm not striking your life
videos you upload
It's not on my channel when people are lying about me, you retarded bitch.
I've only ever told the truth
To signal 66
Crystal you called psycho weirdo for being cool with Brandon
No, I was like
Don't forget that site she called you a weirdo for being cool with Brandon, but she was also
I'm gonna show a video of you in my Discord the other day, laughing about Oliver talking about your fake miscarriages.
You're always gonna be a fucking rabbit.
It's really simple, crystal.
What the fuck do you stalk?
It's zero, bro.
You're not a woman. You're posting me, Crystal, you're stalking me.
I have a fucking woman. I have a vagina. That makes me a woman, you dumb fuck.
You're not a woman. Have you seen her vagina?
Fucking
Unfortunately, we all have my goodness, and will you still have them into your phone you fucking weirdo? No, they're not in my phone actually
No, Wilbur said that to me
People you dumb fuck
You're such a liar you don't like any kind of fucking truth do you Wilbur gave it to me? No, we did it
Really? That's why Wilbur has a video where he said that you threatened him because he wouldn't send you my ta-ta pictures?
No, that's all troubles in.
Wilbur is the body. I never sent it to Wilbur.
No, that's the funny part. That's the funny part.
I never sent it to Wilbur. That's the funny part.
He sent it to me yesterday.
That's how stupid you are.
Tell us when I have it. He sent it to me yesterday.
No, he didn't. You're lying.
Yeah, he did.
Really, that's why me and Wilbur talk privately last night, right? Yeah. Oh, yeah, cuz Wilbur's honest with everyone
It's okay. I want him to lie to you. It's awesome. He's not lying to me. He hates your guts
Okay, good. Yeah, I hate him too. Wilbur will always win against you. I hate him too. Wilbur will always win
Over you
I don't fucking talk about you as much as I want as long as you're stalking me.
Nobody's stalking you, you retarded bitch.
Everyone gather the clips of Crystal praising Gamble, so she's praising the predator.
You're just gonna get striked every time, Crystal.
I'm gonna fucking talk about the truth that's called freedom of speech, you know?
You really think that you can threaten me with anything?
Freedom of speech?
You know what?
It's so funny that you hate the fucking truth.
Anytime you threaten me what's the truth? All you do is lie. No, okay? Everybody's a liar, but you're right
Narcissist right there
You in a lie yesterday. No, like no, no, like
You
I paid you to protect you with me for a month.
You were in my stuff because I was getting in help of you.
Yeah, but you know what?
You don't change.
Oh, you're planning anything.
Oh, guys, what's funny?
His voice came back.
You see?
His octave that was higher, it's not lower again.
What the fuck are you talking about?
You sound psycho.
Okay, you keep supporting predators trip. I don't like you right right. I'm not the one that was on the call with Brandon Q
Dumbass Dumbass Dumbass Dumbass Dumbass and imagine this when I press charge on you fucker
Damn, I'd love for you to show everyone where you sent nudes to me. I would love for you to show that
I'm out of here
Hey, say man, what's up son? I only came out cuz you know
Say what happened where everyone go why did you kick everybody out? I can't get anybody out
Everyone is left
Then you just kicked everybody on
Everyone is I swear. I was actually over at the
You're here. So if I keep there without why are you here?
You're aware I was trying to do a mass unbanned and on my other
I'm gonna do a mass unbanned right now. Hold on a second hidden user. Look. I got it
I'm just gonna unban everybody. Okay, and we'll start all over. Okay. Hey mods. Just keep it. Keep an eye out
You know no doxing no like, you know actionable
explainer state, but all I'm gonna
I'm taking everybody off the hit and was every single person looking at it because there's so many people
Okay, we have somebody else coming. I think I think what you should do is you should just ban everyone
Everybody got
No, I'm not saying you did
That's what happened a kick everybody off. I don't know what happened was sick. I don't know
Say did you kick everybody off crazy? No, you yours only went up there like he's like yeah
I think what you should do you should just ban everyone ban
And then the only viewers that you can have are new completely new people that don't know anyone from before
No, but there'll be the all don't be nothing but all exactly what they'll be people. Yeah
It'll be all you and under your all okay. Well, they're gonna have to act differently. Otherwise, they'll be banned because you'd be able to tell
That's smart. That's a smart. Uh, okay. I'm on banning everyone ban everyone
And everybody
Yeah, I think you ban everyone and you should promote me to the leader
What are you administrative mod?
Administrative model SIG promote me to the manager of the channel
And also hand me over the password to you the AdSense account
The accents, like, all in that way, how you get paid?
Oh, no.
You want to, you want to, you want to, you want to, you want to,
you want to, I'll just forward the money.
Right.
And give me your passport and social security number.
Okay.
Just give me the entire keys to the castle.
Give me a bill.
Give me a bill for your residence that you're living right now.
This is going to be $10,000.
Okay.
I'm gonna I'm gonna file for benefits under psyche's name and every benefit and I'm gonna steal all his benefits
Well, he's living like
And I'm going to steal him from you, but that there you go.
So you could.
So he's going to he's going to pay for your life
while I take your benefits and I sell that shit.
And say, and say, do I get to have sex with you?
I must sell. I must sell your $200 and snap for 100 bucks.
So you have to give it up.
But 300 glow, he's going to be very sad.
It's going to be on sewer slide slide watch what's the sewer slide?
This one you go down this sewer and it just goes on forever and everything is just black
When I talk to you already you never stops you just keep going down
Okay. Wow. Is there anybody backstage? Let me see. Um, no, I'm gonna put the link again guys
Wow, that was, I mean, everyone got kicked out, I didn't mean everyone got kicked out, but yeah.
Yeah, no, it kicked everybody, everybody got kicked out, that's all I was like, what the heck?
I thought you ended the show, I thought you ended the show or something.
I feel here has been having glitches. Are you guys on iPhone? Are you on iPhone? No, I don't have life
I'm on iPhone and I'm having problems stream yard
I've been hearing people saying everybody will iPhone they have problems with it like with the stream yard app
I think I've seen that if you use the browser it starts glitching, you have to use the streamer app.
Oh, okay, then I had it mixed.
And if you're a host, but if you're a host, the app is only for guests.
If you're a host, you still need to use the browser.
So, oh my god, it's still like another 50 people.
I'm just going to go like done right now and then I'm going to...
Although I've been looking at restream and restream seems to be pretty good.
Maybe even better than StreamYard in some ways.
Okay, Restream.
I tried another server.
I mean, Restream natively supports Rumble,
so that's why I'm leaning more towards Restream.
Restream.
Okay, well, I mean, I tried these other servers once
and everyone was mad because it was complicated,
so I'm not sure.
I'm just trying to unban.
Because it was what?
It was too complicated.
And then remember one time I
Off and you were alone up there. I was like people are all smoked out
Yeah, it was you're the only one on so anyway, okay humongous pizza man federal investigator
of autism away with words so nice to meet ya la raims um kevin anthony um fifth six
seven eight nine ten eleven through ninety ninth stage you're all back all the stages
we're back all the stages i mean i have like a thousand stages hit them i mean it's crazy
Imagine me and Janny at your back. Okay, uh, uno lover red balloon. Um, Rob
Yo, you guys know. Oh my god. It's it's uh
Meg's been yo hold on. Hold on
No way, dude
Yo, if i'm not mistaken next month is november, right?
September September September how many months until November September October November two months
30 months. Yeah
Six is gonna come out GT six to come out in November. I thought it was already out digitally. Oh, GT six
No, they're not gonna have oh, actually, I don't know maybe they'll have multiplayer, but they're not gonna
Already have a badass gaming PC. I could play it on my PC, but they're not
And on the GTS, I'm going to have to, uh, basically I'm going to have to buy a PS five w. Okay. Well, can you buy me one?
You guys already have PS fives. I don't have one. I have a computer. GT for GT for Joker has a PS five. You got one.
Yeah, a lot of people got ps5. So are you guys on ps5's? I don't play video games. I don't play
Yeah, just Jen, okay look, I don't know I don't remember what month it is
Well, we're coming up fucking dude the fucking weather has been so fucked up that it's like
Wilbur, I don't know who knows it's probably gonna be it's probably gonna be this hot in November just because
Why are you talking to kids?
Hello, who is this? Why are you talking?
Everybody in here forget that you
Call the 14 year old sexy that you had modest
Oh that's Brandon Q
That's Brandon Q
That's Brandon Q, bro
No, look at Crystal Ang's here
She said that's not the real Wilbur
Yeah, it's a fake Wilbur
Oh my god
That was Brandon Q, bro
That was Brandon Q
I'm so sorry
I can recognize that
I thought it was Ernie and Bert
I thought it was Bert and Ernie
You don't have a ps5 yet. Shit. I gotta get it. I'm gonna get the ps5 pro
I'm not trying to play it
No, I didn't that that person is I did show their ID there at adults
Well, how would they know her age if they haven't seen it?
So they're just like...
Because Brandon Q is trying to project because he's such a big...
Well, let's just see how long it takes for Doofy to stop me.
And saved.
Okay.
Everyone's back.
Everyone has been unhitted.
The chat is now...
Gonna go crazy.
Bye.
Just just just watch the soccer oxy of doofy. Yeah
You these people will not get off your back hooker so they're just like
Who's the leader of it who would it be gamble or it would be that's his new name is doofy doofy, okay
See how he wants to strike any truth of me though. Yeah
I seen it. He came up and just straight up started attacking like and going
Yeah, so he's gonna strike it and keep trying to say take the channel away and yeah
Yeah, that's okay
Yeah, he has to stop stalking stalking is not good at all
Yes. Okay. Stockings bad. Okay.
Yeah. Yeah.
Hey, he's a stalker.
Wow. I believe that.
I believe that.
He hates it because he looks.
I believe that if it's the right
if I'm a psyche or straight guy,
I bet that's like he will stalk them.
Well, do be so stupid.
He couldn't try to bring me down,
but you're going down with me
because you fucking created me.
You dumb fuck.
Well, it's keep an eye on chat cuz I just did a mass unbanned just keep an eye on the Chad
Make sure like
But don't get mad at me when your channel gets struck because of doofy
Dookie, I don't know dookie doofy
Gamble he's ready to fire code word for gambler. Oh, it's a minute
When I come up stand right here, welcome up on the panel.
Doofy's a predator. Doofy's a predator.
Oh my gosh. Doofy, are you being called out? Doofy?
I'm a stalker.
I mean, I don't use anybody with the name Doofy.
You know, Doofy just sounds like a weird name.
You're not the guy from the name
Yeah, that's exactly what I was gonna say
20 minutes, I'm gonna prove you're a liar 20 minutes on my
This dude legit has a tiled mod, bro.
I'm mad that you involve me with brain and cute fuck shit. He's doofy
Yeah, doofy you're a doofy doofy, okay?
Damn, yeah, he's the one from scary movie. He's the one that's retarded and like has a little cop gun
The little water gun and water pisco he thinks is a real cop
It's a blow. Yeah, that's doofy
And you were watching his butthole and dig by yourself in a VC
They're gay together
Me and gloar openly gay
Oh my God, I'm so glad I didn't see Brad as butthole.
Why actually, we'll say that Brad is the stick and the butthole.
You asked to see the butthole.
Crystal, you asked to see his butthole.
No.
Someone said you asked to see his butthole.
Okay.
I wouldn't have done that.
I mean, oh yeah, it was full again.
No, but he was in the VC alone recording it.
Was it clean?
I don't know. I don't remember. I don't remember. Okay. Hey chicken cakes. How are you gonna come up chicken cakes?
I like chicken cakes. I'll put the link down. You're welcome. You're chicken cakes. I like chicken cakes.
even though he doesn't like it very much, I still like it.
Chicken kicks don't help anybody.
Chicken kicks.
Yo, join up, blow.
Sammane, get up here.
I'll step down, I'm like, you know, a couple people come up.
OK, Anita, how did you know that he played a rifle
in his butthole because I didn't see that?
Oh my god, he should have pulled the trigger.
Jesus Christ.
It's not, oh my god, he should have pulled the trigger, yeah.
Hell, yeah, he should have, hell, yeah, he's crazy.
fortune was unloaded i guess right you were there oh no no inset gamble vc was gamble and brandy q
right at least i had other people in my call like a vc you dumb fuck do you think that they
recorded it what the hell did they recorded it yeah without the consent
Oh
They're doing like diddy shit. They're doing like diddy blackmail shit. That's what they're doing like
Yeah, gamble how to freak off with brain and Q
What? Yeah, that's what that's what all these people do psyche did that be the data
They do extortion they do extortion
Brain and Q's butthole
That's some Epstein diddy shit
Isn't he
That's not true, that's crazy
Oh, why are you being like this? Why are you like this way? This is weird. Yeah, you know who didn't want to show his butt hole to me
Brandon Q
Don't even try to put the blame all on me. Get out there with shots back. I
Don't talk about brandy keys but holy mama to throw up. Well, yeah, we'll keep saying I'm besties with it
No, I'm not I've his bubble
Yeah, we have another guest coming up one second the ranged
He's a deranged person along with Gamble. So now it's a deranged
So it's cool. Yeah, so that's cool now
No more even though this dude is doing sick shit. I was doing a monkey upstream this dude is
In a dog conversation monkey Brandon
Yeah, bro. There was no inappropriate, bro. You're talking in a
style, bro. Do everybody gamble? Everybody in this chat? Let it be known that that's cool now.
So why did your name say needle blood? Okay. I thought I thought it was I thought it was
Kermit the Frog. I'm so sorry. Okay. Who was that? Oh, he came up. That was burden Q. He came up
It was a needle blood needle blood. Okay. Oh my god, I sound like a woman. Okay. I might be the same person
Yeah, I don't I'm not a bottom though just yeah, I'm not a bottom. I can't give advice for that
Oh my god, there he is!
He's showing me his butthole backstage!
He did?
Oh my god.
He's showing me his butthole.
It's all poofy.
Oh, he's licking the camera now.
He's bald. Do you know he's bald?
I didn't think he was so bald.
He's eating like a Mexican bird.
Okay, get ready for your next show, Brandon.
Your next butthole show, okay?
I can't look at it anymore.
Okay, look at sick look at sick
What did you hit sick? What is that? Is that dm2?
What is that sick? No, I'm sorry. It says any toe blunt. It says not indeed. It's a knee-toe blunt
Oh, I need to blow okay sick. What are you smoking on? What was that? Chill? I'm not a tobacco
What is it smoking? You know what he's smoking site? You ever seen that before? I've never seen that before
It's a pipe and you put a weed in the end and then you smoke it. It's like it's it looks like a cigar
Hey Arthur come on up Arthur. Oh, okay
I don't want to see his butthole slow dance. I don't want I showed to be back stage
And it's big ball his big balding head
Dude doesn't look like Fred Flinkstone like younger son. Yeah, first Linda was less hair
Read the chat done. Okay. He wants to gamble to be a girl blown out bake lives. Okay. Yeah, he has toilet paper
It's like warm. I know I don't want to see his butthole good. Hey, oh, what's up? Hey, come on up guys
I'm gonna I'm gonna. Oh, yeah, big clips the shock
Okay, I'm gonna post looking good. Oh big clips enjoyed that booty hole shot. He loved it
make lips like he's cook screen shot as Eldo in DMs with Brandon you can come up and defend yourself
Eldo
Hey guys make sure you turn in tune into Brandon Q. I guess he's gonna be exposing me or something like that
Just remember it's all bullshit. You know, yeah, he's just gonna make up lies psyche. You know, he's just gonna make a bunch of lies
Always does it's always lies lies lies
Yeah
Oh, no, no, Brandon, can't this guy's his butthole.
Wow, it's butthole gay guys.
It's butthole.
Wait, what is this person, Josie Grossie?
What are you trying to talk?
What is she saying?
I don't know.
She's gross.
How about we can just wipe this lake clean?
Yeah, can we just wipe it?
Yeah, can you guys all forgive me?
Cause look at all these insane people.
Like, it's not really easy having,
and look at, and then my friend, I'm sick here.
I mean, I love J-Dog, but it's, I mean, sick.
I mean, come on.
Look at this guy. Look at this. Look at this douchebag. Look at this. Look at this egg.
It's so dumb. Hold on.
This egg is a pimp. He says he's a pimp daddy.
Oh my god. What did I do?
You look good. Can I see your nipples, Egg?
Do you want to see my cock?
No, not on the show, but I want to see your nipples.
Bang.
Probably look like a woman's chest.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, everybody.
Wow.
Damn well nobody wants to see that man. It's like wow. Oh shit
Okay, okay
Some crazy shit last yo last night glow had a stream with a hundred viewers
What was glow doing? What was it? What did he do that got gained a hundred viewers?
He had like a e and j bottles
He drank them all by himself or was he with his girl his old lady?
His girl wasn't there. Yeah, his girl wasn't there. She was like she was at her parents house
They got a fight something like that. Oh, he was
No, they were just there was just I don't know. There was they weren't fighting. It was just some
Oh, I thought he was big so he got a drunk as shit
So he got drunk as shit that fool had like a and j bottles now. He had a hundred viewers
His chat wasn't moving
Everybody was moving like crazy like you see how psyche's chats moving. It was moving like five times fast
I was going fast. Well, let's get his
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
You're probably not even bi-curious.
You're just kind of like a little bit of a feminine voice.
Skoro's victim, I don't think so.
I don't think so.
Don't bring up his name again.
You're welcome again, sorry.
Okay, yeah, and it's like, you know, I do it again.
I probably don't apologize to a lot of people
and it's like because I'm stubborn
and I say I don't really like being told what to do
and so I didn't like take out a funnel as much as people.
We have a guest, a special guest here.
Let's welcome Aya next to the chat.
Oh, here we go once again. There you go. Hi. Oh, hey, I'm sorry the other day
You were talking to somebody else named craft or whatever her name was. I thought you were talking to me
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry
Okay, yeah, so it's all
Is on with her lies again about Gamble. Yeah
Sorry, yeah, she's always been like that. She's very to face, you know, she's has a different hidden agenda and she just starts these wars and turns on everybody and plays this game and she doesn't have a boyfriend, you know, that guy is greedy.
That's the same guy that has mental issues that she keeps taking back.
So, yeah, so that's what's going on.
So what happened?
Crystal came on and lied again.
She's playing a dangerous game.
Everybody is already on tour.
We've all been in communication.
And we see what she's doing and she has barbed fooled.
You know, it's just ridiculous, but I doubt Kate is going to have Kate bar up to talk
against Nancy and Jamie, who I think she's friends with or communicates with.
Hello?
You get me up here and then you're gone.
Uh-oh.
I'm sorry, guys.
I don't know what happened.
I don't know what happened here.
I'm going to put the link up again.
I was trying to get back in.
I couldn't get back by back in.
I'm so sorry about that.
Wow, I don't know. I don't know what's going on with the stream yard. I think everyone's crashing out. I'm literally okay
That kicked at the same time. Okay, weird. I don't know what's happening. Okay, so there's the link again. Come on back up guys
Hey, I can use a friend. You want to see the werewolf video? I'll play the werewolf video. This is while we're waiting for people here
Here's a werewolf video. This is when I was turning into a werewolf. I had an old thing
Oh, yeah, I next is back. I'm gonna take a moment, but we'll play with everyone later. Here we go
Hi, sweetie. Yeah, what happened? I was talking. I know my my my myself is acting up today
Ganville is telling the truth and I knew this was gonna happen because she plays these games against him and
She's been like this in the past. He's caught her in so many lies about her fake
Pregnancies and then again recently another fake one
So and then she got caught by Brandon who recorded her being shady just talking about everybody
I haven't contacted her parents. She's insane. Well, did you hear that Brandon showed his butthole to a lot of guys?
No, I'm not surprised. He probably did but I
Gamble was never known as any type of predator
or petto or anything.
It was years ago, he was young
and they did a whole panel.
I don't know if it was a panel,
it was just another group or whatever.
And there was a kid on there
that they were talking to about streaming.
I mean, it's very, it's, I mean,
they used to be a show called
Kids Say the Darnedest Things, okay?
And it was Bill Cosby, I think, or someone, you know,
and they had kids on the show.
And, you know, and actually, Mr. Rogers day kids,
like it's like, it just because there's kids on the show,
there's something called children's programming
and stuff like that where, you know,
There can be kids on the shows.
There's parents that have their kids on YouTube.
And so I don't understand it.
It's like, oh, I mean, I just use my discretion.
I say, you know, 18 or over on the show and stuff like that.
Right.
But just to be safe.
I mean, that person yesterday, I
think that she's a very nice person.
She's an adult.
You know, I did see her ID backstage and stuff like that.
Because people were thinking that she might, you know,
I'm not going to say.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I wasn't really wrong.
They know the girl with the mask, the mask and stuff.
Oh, yeah.
the one that I got confused, I thought he was talking to me and he was talking to the person with the mask. Yeah, yeah. Okay. Yeah. Who was that? Who was that lady with the mask? I think just her name is Rose in the chat and she's like she's she's
just cosplay. She's she does like you know, I think she plays Call of Duty a lot and stuff.
you know, I think she's in college. I think she might be 20 or 21 years old. So I mean,
she's an adult. I mean, it's like, I was allowed to say it and there was nothing.
Oh, I didn't, I didn't even notice. I knew she had some kind of get up on. I didn't know if she
was wearing a mask or what was going on. Yeah, that was a mask. Yeah. But shout out to Genville,
who is telling the truth. I can't believe Crystal turned on him like she does and using Wilbur and
all these other people and doing the, you know,
She's just so two-faced back and forth all these group chats it because I showed proof myself where she was hit me up with Bruno
All these group chats and Bruno says it's chat that had us fight or something. It's like what are you talking about?
It's always you
Well, you know, INX, like, unfortunately, like, you know, and I was going to follow,
I mean, some people give me advice, don't talk about a certain person, but that person is,
again, doxing my family today. Family members saying I need to be institutionalized.
Don't let anybody get you upset or, you know, just leave it alone for now, though. I know you're
upset. Yeah. That person upset. I was upset. Yeah.
and you guys were friends at one time and sometimes when you communicate with them separately it's
like you see a good a good person you know like a real person i mean it's like at the end of the day
i don't have hate in my heart but it's like yeah so remember that your friendship with that person
don't don't pay attention to this bullshit like people with crystal like crystal trying to get
you triggered and fight with these people because that's all she cares about
It's always about being defended or defending somebody and this bullshit crap that she's,
you know, she lives for this shit because she doesn't do real life at all.
It's crystal.
And we don't need people like that, you know, causing problems.
And, you know, that person is hurt, you were hurt.
I mean, you know, we have feelings and I know we go home.
Yeah, we do.
And it's like, and then it's like,
people take advantage of these like little rips
people have sometimes and they get in
and other people get involved to get so complicated.
But I just want to know how are you doing?
How are the cats?
Oh, they're doing great.
You know, and I'm still waiting on that crate.
I'll show you what I got.
Look at what I got yesterday.
You see that in the corner right there?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
that is like a little it's like it's a cat house little cat house oh that is cute yeah
oh wow where did you get that out i need something like that too i'm one room is for them
they got their tunnels and two cat trees yep i got cat trees stuff like that also this is i
recommend this stuff too this is a catnip spray and you can spray it on stuff and the cats will
Yeah, yeah, where'd you get that at? I get it from twoies. Yeah. Yeah, I think I got a friend a friend gave me this
This one is called stimulation for all your cats 10 needs and his cat nip spray and they love this spray a little bit on that
On that one and they love it and stuff
But you know what get a litter box so you know I have to I have litter box
I have one of those electronic litter boxes
I showed it actually the other day because they're saying I don't have a litter box and then I should have freshly scooped
clean litter box. I have a couple actually, including the AM person did bring me a litter box too.
And so I have some, I'll be able to have a cat door that can come in and out and
Lenore, I can go see if I can get Lenore right now, because everyone's saying I ate Lenore,
I killed Lenore and stuff like that, which is very hurtful. Yeah. See if I can grab a real
cat tree back. I showed her last night on the show if you guys are wondering, she's around.
I love that little cat tree back there. I think that's what I need for a boy cat. Yeah.
Guess guess who I got in my arms nor
Yeah, and I would like I would appreciate a retraction for say I killed the north in that version
That would be nice. He tracks it because here. She is right here. She's safe and sound
everybody
See what what happened? She just goes and hides sometimes because I
Right now it's really really hot right now. It's like summer in Los Angeles. It's about 85 degrees. Yeah
Yeah, outside even a night is a little bit warm and she likes a little place
And I believe there's a dog that is barking with the neighbors at this dog
And she kind of likes to like to give the dog the stink guy, you know, how cute. Yeah, there she is
She looks like my bully cat
little because he's a bully cat now I just want to show you guys in case you're worried the door is fine
One was kind of hiding since I brought in that little kitten on July 3rd
You know, but now she's used to her now. She's around her but for a while there
She was hiding herself too like in the closet and
You know, but now she's getting along
Yeah, so I didn't turn into a werewolf like as it was said you could have turned into the full moon broadcast on
July 28th when I was supposed to travel
Actually, it was said I transformed into a woman that night. I
You know, I wouldn't listen in another life
If I was born a woman, it would mean that'd be great, you know?
But I would be kind of an ugly woman, I think, if I was just to...
I mean, I do have a picture of me in drag some place around here.
Have you seen me in drag? Let me see.
No, no, never.
You haven't seen me in ever in that? Okay, let me see.
Uh-uh, no, I didn't know you did that.
Well, I did it for Halloween.
Oh, okay.
Oh, look, I have these treats, too. They're like these things.
Oh, yeah, I get those sometimes. Yeah. Yeah. Well, you want one Lola?
You want one Lola here? You want one Lenore here? Yeah, they love their treats.
Want some? Yeah. Here. She looks like, like littles. Here. Here, lickable treat. Here you go.
And that's Lenore right there, right?
There's Lenore right there, so they're there.
Oh, okay, there's it.
Yeah, okay.
There's your treat right there.
You have one, go on to Lenore, you get one too.
Okay.
Oh, baby.
They're happy.
Yeah, I'm missing Lenore.
There she is so yeah, so what's going now on now with crystal. She's against
Ganville again. What what is her deal? I don't know
Some cement sent to her house. She blames Ganville. She blames. Yeah, I'm gamble for the for the Brandon situation and stuff
Brandon she was the one being shady because that's the type of person she is she's shady as fuck goes back and forth between people
All right. Yeah, oh summer or actually Christine was on a show saying that I have a tape worm
And stuff like that. That's why I'm so skinny. I'm also I was a werewolf the demon
I don't ignore that ignore that where will video annex?
Yeah, I'll just ignore that. I mean
No, I didn't even bother. I hadn't really been watching anything today. I just got back and saw you
I want to show I want to show this real quick if you don't mind. This is this is about
I'm sharing the truth about
About my lycanthropy or something like that. What is it called? I'm a like-in or something
I'm a werewolf. I'm a demon. I'm all kinds of things, but you know what? Yeah at the end of the day
I'm just I'm a human being that with feelings and stuff, but here we go. This is the
Werewolf video enjoy this real quick
See and you might spot some of your faces in this because I have I put some names names and a
Ghosts in this actually I next you can see ghosts in this video. Yeah, here you go
I've been keeping one small secret underneath my tiny hat. I'm a moon-blessed fairy tale werewolf and I'm magical at that
behind the chilies where the enchanted freeway ends with the bird
Certificating glitter rooms and moths as legal friends. It's till the sun itself me. Okay with the period
I'll sue my friendships through then I'll howl into the first what did that
punctuation do
Flickered the lacroix hit the floor our emotional support
She did chicken
Says he's our treasure, but everybody knows the truth. He's an ageless forest oracle in business casual youth during rituals
He raises one immortal hand and says that circle back next quarter to the existential dread
Sister Ali Roth has chosen and vanished in a
Chanel bless she did please don't invent his shoes and
Bring forth all four thinking still the vibes
It's a little bit of a levity right now
I like that one.
Yeah, you like that?
Thank you.
Yeah, I like that video.
You just made that today?
I made that a few days ago.
That was around the time I was about to become a werewolf,
but I turned into a woman instead.
It's really complicated and confusing, but I don't know.
Maybe you can put it.
Figure it out. Let me know. I don't know what I am now. I just have a tape.
Make one of you becoming a Pekingese.
Oh, that's okay. My next one. I want to make one for you.
The dog of the year is a Pekingese.
Yes.
Psych is a Pekingese next. I want to be a Jeff.
That's what Aaron liked. That's why he got that dog and we named him Gizmo
from the movie Gremlins. The person who made the movie Gremlins
So I'm never going to another Chinese knickknack shop
because the first time they said,
oh, we have these cute animals.
And I adopted something named Gizmo,
but I fed him after midnight and he got water on himself.
And he turned into this gremlin creature.
And then another time, I bought a plant.
and it started going to suck my blood
and it turned into this big, this big,
it sounded like Sandman and it sang songs
and it started eating people.
I had to start feeding it people.
Oh no, yeah.
Yeah.
And there's a movie about it called
Little Shop of Horse that I made.
Really?
Yeah, man, yeah, you ought to look into it that
Like this lady was walking a pecan is that you know who I thought I thought of you, you know, yeah, yeah
You are a pecan he's his pecan ease
The pecan ease
Yeah
and so what's up I mean it's like I think I think we had an exciting show
kind of today I'm you know I had gamble on I had I'm gonna watch it yeah earlier
I had just yeah you just rewind the show I'm gonna keep this live up yeah he
was in chat I mean yeah everybody shout out to gamble because what did he do
wrong he didn't do anything but support crystal and try to keep her out of the
Yeah, you know, it's always about ganging up with people defend me. I'll defend you and it's like what's going on do real life
It's not
I've sad news
The couple of the year is broken up. You know beta and salmon are broken up
So really what happened there because he finally opened his eyes to her because she
well I would hope so but actually I think it was because you know he is in love with this guy
named Zaya like he I think he has a crush on some guy and then Zaya was doxing me they dox
beta all over the chat I saw that there was a man of course didn't really care because
he has a crush on Zaya
I mean, Sam and I'll fight you for a day.
I wanna smell Zaya's socks, by the way, and shoes.
Mm-hmm.
I'm sorry if that was gross to people, but you know, I have a sneaker fetish. Yeah
Really, I don't care much for him
No, Zea. Oh, yeah, he's kind of cute, but yeah
I'm just aware of a form guys, could someone send me some some flea medicine, please
Please I mean, I can't I get this tapeworm is getting bigger than me
So I'm just, I don't have a tapeworm.
You know what, she didn't have a tapeworm.
I think some of these people's brains,
brains have some worms in them by now,
but I'm not gonna mention any names.
But yeah, I mean, it's just getting crazy.
But yeah, just ignore and just be you and make it positive. Don't make any dark videos like hey
I don't want to live anymore
No
I was trolling back because that was being said that I mean there's this woman. I think she's I think she might be a registered nurse
I mean she shouldn't be
but she was actually telling me to jump up a bridge
and encouraging another woman
who's a little bit mentally unstable.
No, actually a lot mentally unstable.
She's encouraging her to beat me and kill me
and there would be no karma and no jury would convict her
because I'm just a bad person.
And so that's what I was reacting to,
but everything is taken out of context, especially.
I mean, even like there is this post made that I have a pet cemetery, I sacrifice kittens
and Lola, I'm trying to breed Lola so I can have more kittens for my demonic rituals.
Well, well, well, well, whoever that person that's the bitch, this is to that person.
Hey bitch, Lola's fixed.
She was fixed after she had one litter, okay?
And so she will not be having any more kittens.
and I'd like you to retract your statement.
I'd also like you to retract that I killed Lenore
because as we've all seen, I showed Lenore today.
And so, yeah, so that's it.
I'm gonna wrap up, bye-bye.
But I just wanna thank you so much.
I'll watch from the beginning and stuff.
Yeah, watch from the beginning.
It was an exciting show.
Okay, all right.
You have a good one, all of y'all.
I love you.
Love you too.
Have a good day.
Bye.
And I'm just gonna, I'll play one video the way out.
You know, if anyone wants to watch it, you can.
If not, it's fine, you know.
Actually, I'll, I first want to show you,
this one is actually about the economy of toxicity.
This is why I won't be doing,
I mean, I will accept donations to like,
maybe if I kick somebody off and you want me to have them on,
maybe I'll accept the donation to have them back on.
I'm not really gonna be doing donations to kick anybody
unless maybe I agree with it.
But here's a little, this is their, you know,
this is based on Bita and Sandman's transcripts,
and this is what they do, okay?
So I enjoyed this little short explainer.
Oh my gosh. My mouse is worn out. I can't even click it anymore. Shit. There we go.
As people think of professional live streaming, they picture massive philanthropic stunts and
multi-million dollar giveaways. Or they picture stadiums packed with fans, where professional
gamers compete for massive cash prizes in highly organized sponsored tournaments. But
far away from the sponsors and the stadium lights, there are deeply insulated corners
where traditional gameplay doesn't exist at all.
Welcome to the panelverse.
It's a hyper-niche ecosystem consisting entirely
of open-panel live streams.
There is no video game.
There is no scripted content.
The entertainment is the participants themselves,
crowded onto a single screen, arguing for hours on end.
In a normal broadcast, viewers watch a creator.
Here, the traditional boundaries are erased.
replaced by a ruthless system where every interaction is a transaction centered on confrontation.
The true price of admission is paid into a localized economy
where participants spend real currency to publicly dismantle one another.
To understand how hatred is monetized here, you have to look at a mechanism the community calls
clapping. This chart shows exactly how it works. If a user doesn't like what someone is saying on
the panel or in the chat, they can pay the channel owner roughly $50 to forcibly eject their rival
from the screen. Basic community moderation, usually a tool designed to keep people safe,
is repurposed as a pay-to-win weapon. You are literally buying dominance over another human
And the amounts of money that trigger these brutal conflicts are staggeringly small.
In one recorded instance, a single $10 donation sent to the wrong person
sparked a screaming match that ended a relationship live on stream.
Every interpersonal dynamic is assigned a price tag.
One participant even started charging another user a $100 fee simply to roleplay at her son.
And when she refused to pay, he threatened to take her to collections.
In the panel verse, harassment functions as the primary product,
a core commodity that is aggressively bought and sold across the screen.
To keep those tips and clap fees flowing, the drama can't stay confined to the screen.
It has to continuously escalate.
Participants actively weaponize personal data,
pasting each other's home addresses into the live chat
to incite real-world fear and drive up viewer engagement.
Digital threats rapidly bleed into physical harassment.
It starts with dozens of unwanted food deliveries
and escalates to viewers calling the police to orchestrate
armed emergency responses at a rival streamer's front door.
The psychological toll of this constant surveillance
frequently leads to live, on-air breakdowns.
Creators have been recorded screaming, tearing doors off hinges,
and destroying their own physical surroundings over a hot microphone.
Trust is entirely non-existent.
Users secretly record private phone calls with one another,
then hold those audio files hostage,
dropping cash transfer links in the chat,
while threatening to broadcast the private conversations.
The boundary between the broadcast and physical reality has completely collapsed.
In this ecosystem, a person's real-world safety is just another piece of monetizable content.
The bleakest part of this economy is the financial reality of the people funding it.
Behind the avatars are individuals facing eviction, living in squalor,
or hiding from tens of thousands of dollars in unpaid child support.
This chart compares digital spending against real-world bank balances.
They drain their limited funds to purchase temporary power over strangers.
This creates an endless cycle of addiction.
Desperately paying for digital control only accelerates their financial ruin.
This localized tragedy relies entirely on the infrastructure built by the world's largest tech companies,
whose platforms host and process these toxic micro-economies.
When platforms allow human conflict to be optimized and monetized down to the dollar,
the ultimate price is the total erosion of the user's sanity, privacy, and humanity.
Too hungry to leave us alone
By morning the walls were a silence
And the silence was all that we owned
Ashes fell like snow
Quiet on the ruins below
Covering everything we couldn't save
In a beautiful, merciless glow
I held out my hands to heaven
But heaven had nothing to show
Only the end of everything
Falling like snow
Coat was still there by the window
Window surrendered to flame
For one breath I saw you within it
For one breath the fire knew your name
And all that was ours became weightless, rose black through the shivering air
As if losing life were no different from losing a strand of your hair
Ashes fell like snow, soft were the wildflowers
Turning the earth into winter, and every the truth
The last little proof that I loved you
Falling like snow
What is higher to cold that could burn
It lives where the heat cannot reach it
And waits through the thaw for spring
No ashes fall like snow
And I walk
So let it fall through the darkness
Let it cover the names on the stones
Some things are gone when they're taken
Things are gone
Shape of you here in my MD
All ashes fall like snow